CHANCE CUSACK

TECHNICAL LEAD

PROFILE

Born and raised in New Jersey, I've traveled the world and worked in numerous design and technology fields, both on site and remote. I majored in Creative Arts and Technology, received a BA in Game Development and published numerous titles. I have been the sole post-production manager for a successful photography studio, helped start one business as well as revive >200 others. I currently spend my days ensuring bp is technologically ready for the future.

I am able to do this by providing only the best in service and support by applying an evolving set of skills and best-practices learned over two decades of hands-on experience.

EDUCATION

BA / Creative Arts & Technology

Bloomfield College | 2007 - 2011 Focused on Game Development which provided ground-level access to industry-standard design and development tools, programs, and the application thereof.

Digital Media Production AUCB | 2009-2010

Study abroad semester in Bournemouth, UK. Was taught hands-on digital design skills and techniques, led by industry leaders.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

TECHNICAL LEAD, myIT bar @ bp

HCL Technologies | September 2019 - Present

- Serve as myIT bar technical lead to oversee daily operations and handle complex issue escalations
- Connect with service owners to inform, address and resolve major issues affecting local/global systems
- Assist in development, testing, and maintenance of internal applications and tools
- · Draft documentation supporting new applications and workflows
- Track trending issues and metrics with internal analytics

DESKTOP SUPPORT ENGINEER, myIT bar @ bp

Prosource.it | March 2018 - September 2019

- Provide hands-on support and resolve issues affecting computers, mobile devices, and various other system/server configurations for dozens of end-users per day
- · Perform daily issue and resolution tracking through internal ticketing systems
- Train users in modern technology best-practices

WEB ADVISOR / SOLUTIONS MANAGER

Endurance International Group | Feb 2017 - Jan 2018

Front-line support handling incoming requests for web-hosting related technical issues

- Provided hosting solutions and support for 15,000+ global users
- Solution delivery ranges from client-side programming and design conflicts to server-side compatibility failures
- Absorbed sales responsibility and have exceeded \$30,000 in direct company profit

OWNER | DESIGN / IT SPECIALIST

Project{Radial} | 2011 - Present

Providing tech, design, and IT services. Work includes logo/graphic/web design and development, hands-on hardware/software troubleshooting, as well as emergency repair and support services. Recent clients include:

- Grace Mercy Love GSD Rescue: CTO
 - Managed all aspects of visual design and technology implementation for a local German Shepherd rescue
 - Designed logo, website, social media integrations and back-end server config
 - Streamlined volunteer, donor, and rescue interactions and comms
- Val's Pals GSD Rescue: Web/graphic designer
 - Created an entirely new website for a local German Shepherd rescue

SKILLS

Adobe CS Windows/OSX Linux/Bash HTML/CSS/JS PHP/MySQL Web Design Azure/O365 Break/Fix AWS



CERTIFICATIONS

AWS Cloud Practitioner

In Progress

AWS Solutions Architect Associate

In Progress

CompTIA A+

In Progress

CONTACT

1426 Heathwood Drive Houston, TX 77077 t: 732.239.5410

e: chance.cusack@gmail.com

w: projectradial.com
w: chancecusack.com